BRIAN DUENAS LOPEZ

duenas_brian@yahoo.com | (909) 894-8356 Lake Forest, CA 92630

https://www.linkedin.com/in/duenas-brian | https://brian316.github.io

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Initiative-taking Software Engineer adds high level of experience over 2 years collaborating and working on diverse projects. Enthusiastic, hardworking coder who pulls from active knowledge of current technology landscape to promote best practices in software design.

SKILLS

- Python
- JavaScript
- C++

- Java
- LabVIEW
- MATLAB
- Git
- SQL
- Docker
- GCP
- Linux

WORK HISTORY

Docker Engineer | Life Elixir - Irvine, CA

10/2020 - Current

- Maintain Docker containers for the training and testing of AI model analyses.
- Write scripts to automate the development lifecycle process.

Systems Engineer | Panasonic Avionics

01/2020 - Current

- Monitored and tested application performance for major airline entertainment and communication systems to identify potential bottlenecks, develop solutions, and collaborate with developers on solution implementation.
- Implemented an application to remotely connect and test to the onsite environment allowing Engineers to work from home during COVID.

Front End Web Developer | Milk and Sass - New York, NY

10/2019 - 01/2020

- Took concepts and produced design mockups and prototypes to strengthen designs, enhance user experiences and improve site interactions.
- Completed full redesigns of existing websites to improve navigation, enhance visuals and strengthen search engine rankings.

Software Engineer | CSU San Bernardino - San Bernardino, CA

06/2019 - 09/2019

- Researched, designed and implemented a parking monitor system for information identification, extraction, analysis, retrieval and indexing.
- Created a RESTful API to receive data in real-time, using Python, Flask, GCP.

EDUCATION

California State University - San Bernardino - San Bernardino, CA

Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering

06/2019